(Leonard:)What about it?
Well, the thing is,
the date didn't go that well.
Oh. Too bad. You know...
(Leonard:)I guess the thing to do now is,
you know, pick yourself up.
Dust yourself off, forget it. Move on.
- I can't do that.
- Why the hell not?
Because we're going out again tomorrow.
Excuse me, Stuart?
(Sheldon:)- Have you read the new Flash?
- No.
(Sheldon:)Well, I have,
and it will knock your socks off.
(Sheldon:)Good luck getting them back on.
Anyway, I figure this is probably
my last shot with Penny...
- ...and I don't wanna screw it up.
- Oh, nobody wants that.
So here's my question:
(Stuart:)It's the second date. You think
she'll be expecting things to get physical?
(Leonard:)Oh, gee.
Yeah, my initial reaction is no.
But, you know, let me think about it
and get back to you, okay?
(Stuart:)Okay. So you'll give me a call?
- Yeah, or you call me.
- Great.
(Leonard:)Or nobody calls anyone.
(Raj:)Interesting, Penny's current suitor
asking advice from her former suitor.
Yeah, thanks for closed-captioning
my pain, Raj.
You wanna make sure he gets nowhere
with Penny...
(Howard:)...without jeopardizing your friendship
with either of them?
- I'm listening.
- Just tell him...
(Howard:)...to do everything you've done with her
for the last two years.